Charles R. Martin Photographs, 1945-2011 AIS.2012.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, 1945-1998; II.
  - 35mm Negatives, 1.
    - 1998
      Subjects include the Sunflower Gallery and Al Saul. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Christine Davis, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - Personal- IIIA 3.5 cm elmar & CTD Summar, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Personal- Nicca w/ 1.4 Nikkor, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 31, 33)
      - Personal- Lake Placid- Nicca 1.4 Nikkor, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Personal- Nicca Summar, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 34)
      - Sunflower Gallery- Carol Ann & Jim O'Brien, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 35-37)
      - Personal- M6 1.4 'Lux 35mm, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 38)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 39-40, 45)
      - Sunflower Gallery, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 41)
      - Al Saul, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 42-44)
  - 120mm Negatives, 2.
    - 1945
      Subjects include Landscapes, Military Plane Interior, Portraits, and a Marching Band
      - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1945 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 1946
      - Republic of China, 1946 (Box 71, Folder 2-4)
    - ca. 1960's
      - Personal, ca. 1960s (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
      - Kit- Mexico, ca. 1960s (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - McBeth, ca. 1960s (Box 71, Folder 8-11)
      - McBeth- Musettes, ca. 1960s (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - 1961
      - Foreman Dorsch Bashford & Wallace Greene Middle School, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - 1966
      Subjects include the Boy Scouts of America; McBeth; Chatham College; Insurance.
      - Duke, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 14-15)
      - Personal, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 16, 18, 24-26, 31-32, 34)
      - Insurance Job of 7-8-66- Mars, PA., 1966 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Boy Scouts of America, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 19-23)
      - McBeth, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 27-29, 35)
      - Chatham College, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Porteus, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Mac, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 36-37)
    - 1967
      Subjects include McConnells Mills; McBeth-Geyser; Volkswagen; Alcoa; Point Park; Chatham College; Boy Scouts of America; Holleran-Bldg; Cranberry Industrial Development Corporation (?); Forman, Dorsey, Bashford & Wallace; Mac Modeling; Kit Modeling. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Point Park, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 38-40, 45)
      - Volkswagen, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 41, 72)
      - Personal- Rollei Test, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 42)
      - Personal, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 43-44, 46-49, 53)
      - MAC, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 50-51, 55, 77)
      - C.I.D.C- Wolfe Brush Co., 1967 (Box 71, Folder 52)
      - Gilbert Lumber Copy for Luke, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 54)
      - McConnells Mills, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 56-57)
      - Stuppy, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 58)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 59)
      - Alcoa, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 60-62)
      - Warner, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 63)
      - Boy Scouts of America, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 64)
      - Boy Scouts of America- Guyasuta, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 65)
      - McBeth- Geyser Job, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 66)
      - 613 Ord. Reunion- Mr. Corn 6th Floor Federal Building, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 67)
      - Holleran Building, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 68-70)
      - Waldman- Heathglen, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 71)
      - Hazelwood Community Church, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 73)
      - Foreman Dorsch Bashford & Wallace, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 74)
      - Tom- Amish, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 75-76)
    - 1968
      Subjects include Forman, Dorsey, Bashford & Wallace; Ross Junior High. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Foreman Dorsch Bashford & Wallace, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 78-79)
      - Warner, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 80)
      - Ross Jr. High, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 81)
      - Personal, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 82)
      - Foreman Dorsch Bashford & Wallace- Negative Copies for Murals, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 83)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 84)
      - Foreman Dorsch Bashford & Wallace- Presidents Square Evans City, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 85)
      - Foreman Dorsch Bashford & Wallace- Greene School, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 86-87)
    - 1969
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 88)
    - 1970
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 89)
    - 1971
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 90)
    - 1972
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 91)
    - 1973
      Subjects include the Kellogg Media Group; Phillip Berger & Association; Chatham College; Hampton Township; United Fund; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Cross Electronics; Health & Welfare Association; Community Service Pittsburgh (CSP); Beckman Office; unidentified images. Also included are Martin's personal photographs, passport photos of friends and family, and camera test photos.
      - Personal, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 92-93)
      - Chatham College, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 94, 96-97, 102, 106)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 95)
      - Wilson Passport Picture, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 98)
      - Wilson Passport Picture & Sal, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 99)
      - Beckman Office, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 100-101)
      - Community Service of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 103-105)
      - Health & Welfare Association, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 107)
      - United Fund- Boys Club – McKee's Rock, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 108-110)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 111)
      - Cross Electronics, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 112)
      - Cross Electronics, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - United Fund- Speech & Hearing Society, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- 8th Grade Picture, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - United Fund, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Tessar Rollei Test, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - United Fund- Lions Club, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - United Fund Volunteers- O'Hara Township, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - South Side Business Men- United Fund Volunteers, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Hampton Township Volunteers, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Chatham College, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Phillip Berger & Associates, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Personal- Rollei- Tessar Test, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - KMG- Truck Job, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - GTI- Jack Milligan, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 14-16)
      - KMG- International Truck, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 17-19)
    - 1974
      Subjects include Herr-Voss; Health & Welfare Association; Hugh Stubbs; Chatham; Health Research and Service Foundation (HRSF); Notifier Co.; Mac Modeling; Kit Modeling; Phillip Berger & Association; Fenway Civic Association; Viba-Tech; United Way; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children. Also included are Martin's passport photos of friends and family.
      - Vibra-Tech – Gordon French, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Berger & Associates, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Boy Scouts of America- Fernway Civic Association, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Business Cards- Black Background, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 23-24)
      - Notifier Co.- (Don Jackson), 1974 (Box 72, Folder 25-27, 32)
      - Kit- Modeling, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 28-29)
      - Mac- Modeling, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 30-31)
      - Chatham College Copies- Rachel Carson & Chem Lab, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - Health Research & Service Foundation- Awards, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 34)
      - Hugh Stubbs for Phil Berger, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 35)
      - Health & Welfare Association- Civic Arena, Governor Shapp, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 36)
      - Personal, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 37)
      - Herr-Voss, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 38-39)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 40)
      - Hadley's Passport Picture, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 41)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 42)
      - Windword Swim Team, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 43)
      - PR Pictures, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 44)
      - United Way- Cindy Ritchey, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 45)
      - United Way- Barbara Burns, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 46)
      - Nancy Waters- Copy Work, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 47)
      - Personal- Horses, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 48)
        Two copy slides are also included.
      - Personal- County Fair, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 49)
        Copy slides are also included.
    - 1975
      Subjects include Real Estate Pictures; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; United Way; Bradford Woods Kindergarten. Also included are Martin's personal photographs and passport pictures of family and friends.
      - John Bigelow- Real Estate Picture, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 50)
      - Mrs. Lively Passport Picture, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 51)
      - J.W. (Bill) Shenot- Copy Work, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 52)
      - Empty Sleeves- Dowty, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 53)
      - Kit & Schone, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 54)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 55)
      - Frank Kyes Jr. "Spike", 1975 (Box 72, Folder 56)
      - Sam Law- Int. or LLC., 1975 (Box 72, Folder 57)
      - United Way, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 58-61)
      - R. Morris- Copy Work, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 62)
      - Herr- Voss, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 63)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 64-65)
      - Jefferies Passport Picture, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 66)
      - Gordon French, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 67)
      - Dowty, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 68)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- 8th Grade, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 69)
    - 1976
      Subjects include Health Research and Service Foundation (HRSF); United Way; Boro of Bradfordwoods; North Allegheny Swim Team; Dowty Corp. Also included are Martin's personal photographs, and passport photos of family and friends.
      - United Way, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 70)
      - Davies, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 71)
      - Kit, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 72)
      - Keith Swenson, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 73-75)
      - Dowty Corp.- New Building, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 76)
      - Oberns Passports & Visas, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 77)
      - North Allegheny Swim Team, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 78)
      - Boro of Bradford Woods- Intersection of Bradford & Wexford Run Roads., 1976 (Box 72, Folder 79)
      - Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 80)
      - Leonberger Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 81)
      - Remener Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 82)
      - Martin – Self, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 83)
      - Drobnack Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 84)
      - Shields Passport Pictures, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 85)
      - Bradford Wood CC Publicity, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 86)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 87)
      - Health Research and Service Foundation- Dom Maiello Portraits, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 88)
      - Bogolin Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 89)
      - Alarie Passports & Visas, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 90)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- 8th Grade Picture, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 91)
      - Mowery Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 92)
      - Diane, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 93)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 94)
      - Berger Passports, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 95)
      - I.D. Picture for Real Estate License, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 96)
    - 1977
      Subjects include Bill McDonald. Also included are Martin's camera test images, and passport photos of family and friends.
      - Hays Real Estate- Copy, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 97, 100)
      - Geo. Gilbert S.A.E. Passport Picture, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 98)
      - Charles Wysov (?), 1977 (Box 72, Folder 99)
      - Oranges – For Bill MacDonald, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 101)
      - Bill Straber Passports, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 102)
      - For Atty Fastuca, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 103)
      - Bill MacDonald Advertisement, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 104)
      - Cynthia Davies & Alavie's (?) Son – VISA, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 105)
      - Rev. Tesaro Passport Pictures, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 106)
      - Personal, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 107)
      - Hugh Stubbs- Copy Work, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 108)
      - Luke – Snavely Forest Products, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 109)
      - VT – Instrument Photo Taken, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 110)
      - Bill McDonald- "Cattle Battle" Game, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 111)
    - 1978
      Subjects include Grinnell Co. (Fire Protection); Bradford Woods Kindergarten; Sweetwater Art Center; Ocracoke Island, North Carolina. Also included are Martin's passport photos of friends and family.
      - Berger S.S.U Instrument, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Gerlesley (?) Passports, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Echrich Job, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 3-5)
      - Portrait Picture, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 6-11)
      - Sweetwater Art Center- Copy Work, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Ocracoke- Rollei Test, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Mrs. Gilbert Passports, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Hadley (Visas), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Copy for Roger Sramek (?), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Grinnell, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 18-20)
    - 1979
      Subjects include V. Way; Bradford Woods Kindergarten; John R. Hess Co. Also included are Martin's personal photographs, passport photos of friends and family, and camera test photos.
      - Rollei Test, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Passports Michele Gross, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Personal- Rollei Test, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Tom- I.D. Picture, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - United Way, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 25-26, 28)
      - Mrs. Williams, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - John R. Hess Co., 1979 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Copy for Liz, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - Passports, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - Mrs. Burns- Passports, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Copy Job, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - Personal- Modeling Shots, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 35-40)
    - 1980
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; Kmart; Elks Lodge; Bradford Woods Kindergarten; Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children. Also included are Martin's passport photos of friends and family, and camera test photos.
      - Bette Roth, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 41)
      - Elks, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 42-44)
      - Berger, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 45-46)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 47, 51-54, 56-65)
      - Bradford Woods Kindergarten, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 48)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- 1980 Sr. Class (Box 73, Folder 49)
      - Rollei- Test, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 50)
      - Passports- Dick & Betty Kehew, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 55)
      - Kmart, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 66-67)
    - 1981
      Subjects include Kmart; Hugh Stubbs Co.; Dynamic Equipment; Red Cross; China. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Rollei Test on Focus points, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 68)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 69-71, 74-80, 82)
      - Kmart, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 72)
      - Hugh Stubbs Co., 1981 (Box 73, Folder 73)
      - Red Cross, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 81)
    - 1982
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment Co.; Kmart; Kit Modeling. Also included are Martin's personal photographs and passport pictures of friends and family.
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 83, 85, 87, 89-90)
      - Personal- Test, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 84)
      - Kit- Copy of Wedding Procession, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 86)
      - Kmart- West View Park, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 88)
      - Ann Treamer, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 91)
      - Nancy Williams Passports, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 92)
      - Dale Newman, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 93)
      - Greene Passports, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 94)
    - 1983
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment.
      - Dynamic Equipment Coporation, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 95, 98)
      - For Alice Snyder, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 96-97)
      - Portrait Picture & Machinery, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 99)
      - Machinery, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 100)
    - 1984
      Subjects include Copper & Brass Sales; Dynamic Equipment; Hot Harry's North Park Runners. Also included are Martin's camera test photos.
      - Hot Harry's North Park Runners, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 101)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 102, 109)
      - Personal- 3.5 Tessar Rollei Test, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 103)
      - Personal- Rollei Test, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 104)
      - Machinery, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 105, 111)
      - Personal, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 106)
      - Rollei Xenar Test, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 107)
      - Xenar Collar Test, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 108)
      - Copper & Brass Sales- Dan Stein, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 110)
      - December Job- Machinery Equipment, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 112)
    - 1985
      - Hot Harry's & Snow, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 113)
      - Hot Harry's- Group Shot, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 114)
      - Machinery Equipment, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 115)
      - Aerial View of Bradford Woods, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 116)
      - Sigma Chi Fraternity- St. Barnabas, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 117)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 1, 5, 6)
      - Pentax Test, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Gatan/ ACOCCA Book, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Gatan/ ACOCCA Shot, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Machinery Equipment, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 1986
      Subjects include Hot Harry's; Dynamic Equipment; Red Valve. Also included are Martin's passport photos of friends and family.
      - Hot Harry's 1986 Valentine's Day (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 9, 12-13)
      - Reverend Tessaro P.R. Picture, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 10-11)
      - Valve Job, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Red Valve, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - 1987
      - United Way- Mr. Dickerson, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 16-17)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Machinery Equipment, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 19, 38)
      - Bill Bell- Copy Work, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Bill Bell- Copies after Retouching, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Hot Harry's Club, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation- Remodeled 1919 Machine, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Personal- Passport Pictures, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Personal- Macs Passport Picture, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Personal- Rollei 2.8 Test, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Personal- 3.5 Tessar Rollei Test, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Personal- Bronica Test, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - BDAT, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Factory/Construction Workers, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 30)
      - Personal- Copies of Mac's Triathlon Pictures, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 31)
      - BDAT- Super Industries, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 32-35)
      - Super Industries- Allegheny Ludlum- Natrona, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 36)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association- Mayor w/ Group, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - 1988
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; St. Barnabas; Sweetwater Art Center; Industrial Ceramics Inc.; Murray Agency; Pittsburgh Blind Association; S. A. E.. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 39-40, 59)
      - Society of Automobile Engineers- Book Copies, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 41-43)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association- Safety Vests & Flag, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 44-45)
      - Murray Agency- Ross Township Office & Wexford Office, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 46)
      - Murray Agency- Ann Murray – Recruiting Picture, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 47)
      - Murray Agency- Zelienople Office, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 48)
      - Personal- Bernice, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 49)
      - Bob Newman- Book Jacket Picture, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 50)
      - Personal- Test & VISA Picture for Sal, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 51)
      - Old Post Office, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 52)
      - Wright (Helen) Copies of Old Photo, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 53)
      - Personal- Field Trip- McConnell's Mills, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 54)
      - St. Barnabas- Copies of P.R. Photo & McConnell's Mills, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 55)
      - Sweetwater- 1988 Christmas Angels (Box 74, Folder 56)
      - Sweetwater Egg Zone Shots- Class Group Shots, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 57)
      - Industrial Ceramics Inc., 1988 (Box 74, Folder 58)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association- Night Shots- Safety Vest & Flag, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 60)
      - Pittsburgh Blind Association, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 61-64, 66-72)
      - G.E. for Jack Roehl, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 65, 74)
      - Al Saul Artworks Copies & Ritchie, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 73)
      - Personal, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 75-76)
    - 1989
      Subjects include Dynamic Equipment; Scenic; T. Murray; V.T.;P.R. Shots; Abbot Ross; St. Barnabas; Bio-Energetiks; Robertson Heating Supply; Murray Agency; RTG5. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Murray Agency, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 77, 87)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 78, 89-92, 100)
      - P.R. Shots- Pam Huilele (?), 1989 (Box 74, Folder 79)
      - Prototype New Seismograph, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 80)
      - Personal- Ocracoke Easter '89, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 81)
      - Personal- Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 82)
      - Personal- Waterfall Images & Family, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 83)
      - Jillian Daniels And Misc, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 84)
      - Route 65, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 85-86)
      - Iris & Bernice, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 88)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Map, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 93-94)
      - Murray Agency- Cranberry Office, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 95)
      - Bio-Energetiks- Perrysville Office, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 96)
      - Robertson Htg Supply, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 97)
      - Personal- Hells Hollow & Bill, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 98)
      - Personal- Nature Images, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 99)
      - St. Barnabas- Nurse's Aides, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Hells Hollow, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Personal- Tom's Tenant, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Personal- McConnell's Mill, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Personal- Nature Images, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Dynamic Equipment Corporation, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Holland- Copy of Old Photo & Test, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Abbot Ross, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 8-9)
      - Crete, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - 1990
      Subjects include Murray Agency; McCauley Medical Association; St. Barnabas PR. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Murray Agency- Ross Township Office, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Felicity Weber- Dancer, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 12-13)
      - Al Saul- Copy Work, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Unidentified Assisted Living, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 15, 17)
      - Mary Geyer, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - Meeting & Unidentified Assisted Living, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      - St. Barnabas- PR Release Picture, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 19)
      - Personal- Sal, Pictures for Murray Agency, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 20)
      - P&D Health Products (Pat Nudi)- Ortho-Ice, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 21-22)
      - Personal- Xenar Rollei- Laurel Highlands, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 23-24)
      - McCauley Medical Associate, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 25-27)
      - Julia Tausen Copies- (Peter Tausen in Tunisia 1920-25), 1990 (Box 75, Folder 28)
      - Murray Agency- Wexford Office, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Pat Nudi, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 30)
      - Health Products- (Pat Nudi), 1990 (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - Murray Agency- Cranberry Office & Presentation of Essay Awards, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - Murray Agency- Cranberry Office, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 33)
      - No Smoking Sign, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - Lilypad, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 35)
      - Trees, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 36, 38)
      - Trees and Leaves, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - 1991